



Vittorio Picone

Nationality: Italian (+39) 3922016432 **Date of birth:** 30/07/2002

Email address: vittoriopicone30@gmail.com

♦ Website: www.github.com/viksn0w **♦ Website:** viksn0w.github.io

O Instagram: www.instagram.com/viksn0w

O Instagram: www.instagram.com/viksn0w.design

▼ Twitter: www.twitter.com/viksn0w1

• Address: Via Vasca Cozzolino 56/C, 80040 Pollena Trocchia (NA) (Italy)

ABOUT ME

In my programming experience, I worked with C / C ++ since 2018 and I am now learning the Vulkan API and the concepts on which it is based; I'm also in the iOS application development field since 2015 and I am currently studying Metal and MoltenVk. The recent assignments, job requests and my course of study have provided me with advanced Full Stack developer skills in SQL, PHP, JS, HTML and server configuration (XAMPP Suite).

I studied and worked for a total of 6 months abroad, in Ireland and the United Kingdom with assignments and studies always aimed to the computer science field with a particular focus on team work, obviously in English, and on technical English. I also add another three months of the C1 English certification course.

I am in the field of CGI since 2018, creating 3D posters, specialised in hyper realism and creation of realistic materials; I have an advanced knowledge of blender and its components and an intermediate knowledge of Final Cut Pro

WORK EXPERIENCE

Database and resolutions dogwatch | Disservice advisor

Accenture [24/07/2022 - 05/09/2022]

City: Naples **Country:** Italy

Disservice advisory: if a disservice, front end side mostly, is present, I analyse the issue and pass the obtained pieces of information to the competent team.

Database and resolutions dogwatch: fixing and improving queries; analysing the records from the queries and if there are some errors, fix them if it's my field of competence or pass the error to the competent team.

Full Stack Developer | Java Back End Developer

3F & EDIN [08/05/2022 - 24/07/2022]

City: NA - Napoli Country: Italy

Server-side programming in Java, Node.JS and SQL; Angular as front-end framework. I've done many projects and services such as a management application for a gym and an ordering application for restaurants.

Full Stack Developer

Pointel - Alilauro [16/09/2021 - 16/04/2022]

City: Napoli

Country: Italy

Server-side programming in PHP, Python and SQL and front end in JavaScript. The project, named internally as Alitrack, aims to monitor and geolocate various types of marine ships.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Young Business Manager Certificate Plus

UCD - University College Dublin [02/06/2018 - 29/08/2018]

Address: Belfield, Dublin 4, Dublino (Ireland)

Field(s) of study: Information and Communication Technologies

Team Working Computer Science related management Business Management

Trinity College - B2 / Computer Science Related English and Management

Christ Hospital College [06/06/2019 - 02/09/2019]

Address: RH13 OLJ Horsham (United Kingdom)

Field(s) of study: Information and Communication Technologies

General:

- In-depth study of the English language
- In-depth study on Anglo-Saxon habits

Specifications

- In-depth study of the English language in the IT field
- In-depth study on marketing related to the IT field

ESB - C1

ESB - Study Tours [15/07/2020 - 30/07/2020]

Degree of Istituto Tecnico Settore Tecnologico Indirizzo "Informatica e Telecomunicazioni" articolazione "Informatica" (Computer Science)

ITI Enrico Medi [11/09/2018 - 25/06/2021]

Address: Via Buongiovanni, 84,, 80046 San Giorgio a Cremano (NA) (Italy)

www.itimedi.it

Field(s) of study: Computer Science

Final grade: 100 - Level in EQF: EQF level 5

National classification: TOP 9.9% – Type of credits: Crediti Scolastici Superiori – Number of credits: 100/100

Systems and Networks, Technology and Design of computer systems, programming in C / C ++, Assembly 8086, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP. In the final phase of the path, the study was concentrated on full stack development and server configuration via XAMPP. Principles of Telecommunications and Electrotechnics

Bachelor in Computer Science

University of Naples "Parthenope" [10/09/2021 - Current]

Address: Via Ammiraglio Ferdinando Acton, 80, 80133 Naples (NA) (Italy)

https://international.uniparthenope.it

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Italian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C2 READING C2 WRITING C2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C2 SPOKEN INTERACTION C2

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

Linux / PHP / MySQL / HTML / Windows / C++ / C / Microsoft Office / SQL / CSS / Android / Python / Git / Javascript / Mac / macOS

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: AM 11/01/2021 - 11/01/2031

Driving Licence: A2

Driving Licence: B 01/01/2021 - 01/01/2031

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Rugby

Enrolled at: UCD - Vesuvio - Partenope

Played in: Dublin - Naples Duration: 2017 - 2022

Additional information: hook 5

COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Communication and interpersonal skills

- Excellent communication skills
- Excellent relational teamwork competences acquired during internships abroad.